University Senate; Records ua200
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Legislation, 1966-2018; 3; 3.5 cubic ft.; 505 Digital Files
  - 1977-1978 Academic Year Legislation, 1977 July-1978 June
    - 7778-04: Smoking Policy - Returned to Council - Approved - March 6, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 7778-05: Dropping a Course - Approved - December 5 Revision - Approved - March 6, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 7778-06: Repeating Courses - Approved - December 5, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 7778-07: Final Examination Retention Policy - Returned to Council - March 6 Revision - Approved - May 1, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 7778-08: Amendment to the Calendar Guidelines - Approved - March 6, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 7778-09: Student Representation on the Senate - Approved - April 3, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 7778-10: Certificate Program in Library & Information Science - Approved - April 3, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 7778-11: Revised Requirements for the Business Administration Program - Returned to Council - April 3 (Accepted as a council report), 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 7778-12: Undergraduate Academic Grievance Procedures - Approved - May 1, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 7778-13: Structured Second Fields - Approved - May 1, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 7778-14: Charge to the Council on Research - Approved - May 1, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 7778-15: Statement of Principle - Approved - May 1, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 7778-16: Establishment of a Dissertation Faculty - Defeated - May 15, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 7778-17: Dropping a Course - Approved - May 15, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - 1976-1977 Academic Year Legislation, 1976 July-1977 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 7677-01: Voter Registration - Approved - September 13, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 7677-02: Composition of SCRUE - Approved - November 1, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 7677-03: "Deterrence" Patrols - Approved - December 6, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 7677-04: Amendment to Firearms Policy - Defeated - February 7, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 7677-05: Support for March 15 Demonstration - Approved - March 7, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 7677-06: Amendment to Firearms Policy - Approved - April 11, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 7677-07: Student Representation on the Senate - Approved - April 11, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 7677-08: Composition of the Student Affairs Council - Approved - April 11, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 7677-09: Undergraduate Major in Public Affairs - Withdrawn - May 2 - Approved - September 19, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 7677-10: Academic Retention Standards - Approved - May 2, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 7677-11: Council on Promotions and Continuing Appointments - Defeated - September 19, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 7677-12: Master of Arts in Liberal Studies - Approved - September 19, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - 1975-1976 Academic Year Legislation, 1975 July-1976 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 7576-01: Amendment to the Composition of the Council on Promotions and Continuing Appointments - Approved - September 22, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 7576-02: Revision in the Charge of the Council on Academic Freedom and Ethics - Returned to Council - Approved - November 3, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 7576-03: CAFE Complaint Procedures - Approved - December 8, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 7576-04: "Z" Grade - Returned to Council - February 9, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 7576-05: Amendment to CAFE Complaint Procedures - Approved - February 9, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 7576-06: Patent Waiver Policy of SUNY Research Foundation - Approved - March 8, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 7576-07: Funding Rally - Approved - March 8, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 7576-08: Course Withdrawal for Undergraduate Students Approved - April 5, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 7576-09: Amendment to Faculty By-laws - Approved - April 5, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 7576-10: Faculty Workload - Tabled - April 5 - Returned to Council - May 3, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 7576-11: Library Council - Approved - May 3, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 7576-12: Membership on the Council on Educational Policy - Approved - May 3, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - 1974-1975 Academic Year Legislation, 1974 July-1975 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 7475-01: Proposed Revisions in Guidelines for Promotion and Continuing Appointment - Approved, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 7475-02: Transfer Credit for Balanced "D" - Approved, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 7475-03: Part-Time Full-Status Appointments Within the Tenure System for Teaching Faculty - Approved, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 7475-04: Resolution on Parking - Tabled, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 7475-05: Statement of Belief Regarding the 1974-1976 Contract and Self-Governance at SUNYA - Approved, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 7475-06: 1976-1977 Academic Calendar - Approved, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 7475-07: Teaching Awards - Approved, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 7475-08: Final Examination Policy - Approved, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 7475-09: Resolution Regarding Outstanding Teacher Award - Approved, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 7475-10: Conduct and Responsibility of Instructional Staff - Referred back to Council, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 1973-1974 Academic Year Legislation, 1973 July-1974 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 7374 Proposed Bills and Resolutions, 1973 January-1974 December (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 7374-01: Rules of Order - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-02: Academic Calendar for 1975-1976 Academic Year - Referred to Committee - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-03: Composition of Council on Promotions & Continuing Appointments - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-04: Composition of Council on Promotions & Continuing Appointments - Defeated, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-05: Indian Quadrangle Dining Area - Referred to FSA, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-06: Outstanding Teacher Award - Referred to Committee - Withdrawn, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-07: Campus Firearms Policy - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-08: Examination of Student Medical Records - Referred to SAC, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-09: Dean's List - Criteria - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-10: Amendment to 1973-1974 Academic Calendar - Defeated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-11: Permanent Representation of Students on University Senate - Withdrawn, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-12: Amendment to Guidelines for Preparing the University Calendar - Withdrawn in favor of 7374-15, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-13: Reconsideration of Tenure Decisions - Defeated, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-14: Reconsideration for Continuing Appointment - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-15: Amendment to Guidelines for Preparing the Academic Calendar - Referred to Committee - Defeated, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-16: Reconsideration After the Mandatory Year - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-17: Reconsideration of Continuing Appointment Decisions Made in 1972-1973 - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-18: Consideration for Continuing Appointment - Defeated, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-19: Alumni House & Environmental Protection - Referred to UCC, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-20: University Car Pool Program - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-21: Revisions in Campus Bus Schedule - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-22: Regulation of Pets on Campus - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-23: Resolution on Tuition - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-24: Resolution on Parking - Withdrawn, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-25: Policy for Carrying Firearms on Campus - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-26: Amendment to the Rules of the Senate - Defeated, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-27: Jurisdiction of Schools & Colleges in Establishing Academic Policies - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-28: Pre-Registration and Registration Procedures - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-29: Submitting Grades to Registrar - Defeated, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-30: Amendment to Senate Implementation of the By-Laws - Tabled, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-31: Date for "W" Grade - Defeated, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-32: Reversal of Prior Recommendation - Tabled, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-33: Amendment to the Charge of the CPCA - Tabled, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-34: Resolution on Operational Guidelines - Tabled, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-35: Student Participation in Promotion & Continuing Appointment Recommendations - Tabled, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-36: Evaluation of Teaching - Tabled, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-37: Student-Faculty Committee on Teaching - Tabled, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-38: Performance Expectations - Tabled, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-39: Personnel Committee - Tabled, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-40: External Letters - Tabled, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-41: Confidentiality of Personnel Proceedings - Tabled, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-42: University Fountains - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-43: Bachelor of Arts Major in Judaic Studies - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 7374-44: Bachelor of Arts Major in Puerto Rican Studies - Approved, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - 1972-1973 Academic Year Legislation, 1972 July-1973 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 7273-01: Guidelines for Academic Calendars - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 7273-02: Due Dates for Students' Bills - Referred to Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 7273-03: Opinion Poll - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 7273-04: Council on Promotions and Continuing Appointments - Defeated, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 7273-05: Academic Calendar - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 7273-06: Executive Committee - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 7273-07: Amendment to Bill 7172-24 - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 7273-08: Emeritus Status - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 7273-09: Dormitory Inspection Policy - Referred to Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 7273-10: Undergraduate Grading - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 7273-11: Undergraduate Grading - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 7273-12: Undergraduate Grading - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 7273-13: Undergraduate Grading - Defeated, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 7273-14: Undergraduate Grading - Defeated, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 7273-15: Academic Rank Emeritus - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 7273-16: Undergraduate Grading - Correction - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 7273-17: B.A. with a Major in Greco-Roman Classical Civilization - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 7273-18: Graduation Requirements - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 7273-19: Alumni House - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 7273-20: Privileges of the Rank Emeritus - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 7273-21: Tuition Waiver Ceiling - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 7273-22: Dean's List and Graduate with Honors - Section 1 Renumbered as 7374-09 - Approved, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 1971-1972 Academic Year Legislation, 1971 July-1972 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 7172-01: Priorities - September 13, 1971 - Referred to CEP - October 4, 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-02: Membership on Grievance and Complaint Committee - September 13, 1971 - Defeated, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-03: Council and Committee Attendance - September 13, 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-04: Membership on Council on Educational Policy - October 4. 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-05: Reprimand to Undergraduate Academic Council - October 4, 1971 - Withdrawn for 5-C, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-05-C: Undergraduate Grading - October 4, 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-06: Membership on the Undergraduate Academic Council - October 4. 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-07: Membership on the Student Affairs Council - October 4, 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-08: Group Automobile Liability Insurance - November 8, 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-09: Academic Calendar - November 8, 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-10: Membership in SPA - November 8, 1971 - No Action - December 13, 1971 - Withdrawn, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-11: Academic Calendar for 1972-73 - December 13, 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-12: "Three Year Baccalaureate" - December 13, 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-13: Money for SUNY Senators - December 13, 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-14: Term Appointment Renewal - December 13, 1971 - Returned to Comm. - January 31, 1972 (Revised) - Returned to Comm. - February 28, 1972 (Revised) - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-15: College Level Examination Program - December 13, 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-16: Physical Education Proposal - December 13, 1971 - Defeated, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-17: Change in Wording of Student Guidelines - December 13, 1971 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-18: Use of Volunteers in Library - December 13, 1971 - Tabled, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-19: Semester Hours - February 28, 1972 - Defeated, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-20: Decision-Making With Regard to Educational Policy - February 28, 1972 - Adopted, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-21: Tuition Policy - February 28, 1972 - Defeated, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-22: Determination of Prior Service Credits - March 27, 1972 - Withdrawn, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-23: Consideration for Continuing Appointment - March 27, 1972 - Postponed - May 19 1972 - Referred to EPC - Withdrawn, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-24: Senate Councils - March 27, l972 - Postponed - April 17, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-25: Council on Educational Policy - March 27, 1972 - Postponed - April 17, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-26: Undergraduate Academic Council - March 279 1972 - Postponed - April 24, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-27: Graduate Academic Council - March 279 1972 - Postponed - April 24, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-28: Student Affairs Council - March 27, 1972 - Postponed - April 24, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-29: Council on Research - March 27, 1972 - Postponed - April 24, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-30: Academic Services Council - March 27, 1972 - Postponed - May 11 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-31: University Community Council - March 27, 1972 - Postponed - May It 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-32: Council on Academic Freedom and Ethics - March 27, 1972 - Postponed - May 1, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-33: Council on Faculty Promotions and Continuing Appointments - March 27, 1972 - Postponed - May 13, 1972 - Referred to EPC, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-34: Council on University Evaluation and Improvement - March 27, 1972 - Postponed - May 11 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-35: Physical Education Requirement - March 27, 1972 - Referred to Undergraduate Acadmic Council - May 1., 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-36: Undergraduate Grading - May 19 1972 - Postponed, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-37: D. A, in Spanish - May, 8, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-38: Guidelines Concerning Promotions and Continuing Appointments - May 8, 1972 - Referred to EPC, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-39: Change in Trustees' Policies Concerning Term Appointments - May 9, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-40: Ad Hoc Committee on Teacher Evaluation - May 9, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-41: Change in Membership of Council on Educational Policy - May 9, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-42: Affirmative Action - May 9, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-43: Inclusion of Past Chairman of the Senate on the Senate - May 9 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172-44: Interdisciplinary Major - September 5, 1972 - Approved, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 7172 Proposed Bills and Resolutions, 1972 January-1972 December (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - 1970-1971 Academic Year Legislation, 1970 July-1971 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 7071-01: Powers of the University Senate - Approved - September 21, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-02: Right of Faculty Member to Appear Before Council on Promotions and Continuing Appointment - Tabled - September 21, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-03: Election of Committee on Nominations and Elections - Approved - September 21, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-04: Chairman of the University Senate - Approved - September 21, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-05: Quorum of Senate - Approved - September 21, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-06: Religious Holidays - Approved - September 21, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-07: Committee on student and Faculty Roles During Demonstrations and Confrontations - Defeated - October 19, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-08: Appearance of Faculty Members Before Groups Considering Their Promotion or Continuing Appointment and Notice of Departmental Action - Approved - October 19, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-09: Time in Rank for Promotion to Associate Professor and Professor - Approved - October 19, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-10: Off-Campus Greek Housing - Approved - October 19, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-11: Change in Student Affairs Council Membership - Approved - October 19, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-12: To Revise the Inter-Institutional Cross-Registration to Include Graduate Courses in Albany Law School - Approved - November 23, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-13: To Change Graduate Student Membership on the Graduate Academic Council - Approved - November 23, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-14: Notification of Departmental Recommendation Concerning Continuing Appointment - Approved - November 23, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-15: Waiver of Mandatory Consideration for Promotion - Approved - November 23, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-16: Suspension of Current Traffic Violation Disciplinary Action Procedures (Students) - Withdrawn - November 23, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-17: Parking Policy for the University - Approved - November 23, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-18: Extension of Current Senate Structure - Approved - December 7, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-19: Outstanding Teacher Award - Approved - December 7, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-20: Correction of Inequities in Faculty Salaries and Fringe Benefits - Approved - December 7, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-21: Multiple Major - Referred to Committee -, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071 Resubmitted as "Double Major" - Approved - January 25, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-22: Approval of Ph.D. in German - Approved - January 25, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-23: Temporary Commission on Area College Cooperation - Approved - January 25, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-24: Outstanding Teacher Award Guidelines - Approved - March 22, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-25: Establishment of a Faculty Lounge - Withdrawn - February 15, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-26: Ph.D. in Library Science - Approved - February 15, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-27: Ph.D. in Anthropology - Approved - February 15, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-28: Area College Cooperation - Approved - March 22, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-29: Stop Signs - Withdrawn - March 22, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-30: Ph.D. in Social Welfare - Approved - April 19, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-31: D.A. in Economics - Approved - April 19, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-32: D.A. in English - Approved - April 19, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-33: D.A. in Physics - Approved - April 19, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-34: Judaic Study Year in Israel Program - Approved - April 19, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-35: Interim Plan for Graduate Student Representation - Defeated - April 19, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-36: Change in Name of the School of Library Science - Approved - May 3, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-37: Guidelines Concerning Promotion in Rank and Continuing Appointment - Approved - May 3, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-38: Environmental Studies Program - Approved - May 3, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-39: Second Field - An Interpretation Approved - May 3, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-40: B.S. Major in Social Welfare - Approved - May 3, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-41: Student Evaluations - Withdrawn - Referred to CUE & I, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-42: M. A. in Afro-American Studies - Approved - May 14, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-43: Ph.D. in Geology - Approved - May 14, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-44: B.A. Major in Music, General Program - Approved - May 13, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 7071-45: B.S. Major in Business Education - Approved - May 13, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - 1969-1970 Academic Year Legislation, 1969 July-1970 June
    - Summary of Legislation for 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 6970-01: Collection of Faculty Dues - Approved - September 29, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 6970-02: Grading System - Approved - October 27, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 6970-03: Parking - Approved - October 27, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 6970-04: Disciplinary Removal from Residence - Approved - October 27, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 6970-05: Report of the Ad Hoc Faculty- Student Consultation Committee - Returned to Committee - October 27 - Approved - February 16, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 6970-06: Inter-Institutional Registration - Approved - November 17, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 6970-07: Report from the CPCA - Tabled - November 17, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 6970-08: Recommendations of the Ad Hoc Faculty- Student Consultation Committee - Tabled - November 17, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)